A Guide to the Burton-Neighbors Addendums 1982
Roanoke Public Libraries
Roanoke Public Libraries
A Guide to Burton-Neighbors Addendums
Roanoke Public Libraries
2011.9.1
1 record storage box
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
Donated by Babe Fowler
Scope and Content
The Burton/Neighbors Addendums Collection is comprised of materials related to families, landowners, and soldiers from the Botetourt County area. The collection includes a spiral bound notebook, 1 journal publication, loose leaf documents and newspaper clippings, 3 bound folders, and 11 loose folders. The information is both in print and handwritten.
Arrangement
Items are arranged by size and type.
Contents List
- Burton-Neighbors Addendums (Box 1)
  - 1782 Landowners of Botetourt County: One spiral-bound notebook undated (Folder 1)
  - The Report: A Journal of German-American History 1982 (Folder 2)
  - Botetourt County First Surveys prior to 1770 undated (Folder 3)
  - Roanoke County 1838 Tax List/Marriages, 1850 Census Mortality Schedule undated (Folder 4)
  - Revolutionary Records: Some Soldiers of Franklin, Bedford, Montgomery and Amherst Counties 1948-1949 (Folder 5)
  - Records compiled by the William Preston Chapter of Daughters of the American Revolution undated (Folder 6)
  - Montgomery White Sulphur Springs: Clipping from Forum 1982 (Folder 7)
  - Massacre at the Meadows by Mary Musselwhite De Noya: article from the DAR Magazine 1972 (Folder 8)
  - Colonial Wars and Revolutionary Soldiers in Botetourt County: handwritten notes undated (Folder 9)
  - Botetourt County Wills, Agreements, Inquests, Powers of Attorney and Indentures: handwritten notes undated (Folder 10)
  - Botetourt County Deeds for Want of Tax: handwritten notes undated (Folder 11)
  - Botetourt County Will Books to 1850: handwritten notes undated (Folder 12)
  - Botetourt County Surveys: handwritten notes and aerial photograph undated (Folder 13)
  - Betty Lou O'Conner Newlanden: Pedigree Chart undated (Folder 15)
  - Botetourt Businesses Advertized in Herald of the Valley: handwritten notes undated (Folder 16)
  - Botetourt County Court Records: handwritten notes undated (Folder 17)
  - News clippings about Gene Crotty, author undated (Folder 18)
  - Botetourt County Survey and Plats: handwritten notes undated (Folder 19)
  - Jones Research and copy from History of Patrick and Henry Counties by Virginia and Lewis Pedigo, 1933 undated (Folder 20)